<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SHERLOCKED</string>


    <string name="s1e1">The brilliant opener that took TV by storm, in which veteran military medic
          Dr John Watson finds his thirst for adventure
           fulfilled by his new flatmate, the genius consulting detective Sherlock Holmes, on the trail of a pill-popping serial killer taxi driver who works for… Moriarty! Loosely based on A Study in Scarlet.

    </string>


    <string name="s1e2">Called in by an old friend to investigate a break in at a city bank, Sherlock stumbles upon murder and heavily encoded mystery as he and Watson pursue a gang of Chinese smugglers desperate to get their hands on a stolen priceless treasure. Once again, the closing moments revealed a mysterious criminal sponsor known only as…M!</string>
    <string name="s1e3">Commissioned by Mycroft to investigate the death of a government employee Sherlock solves a series of linked mysteries that culminate in his first-face-to-face encounters with his nemesis Moriarty – and a memorably tense bomb-vest Mexican standoff at an atmospheric Victorian swimming baths.</string>
    <string name="s2e1">The great deducer meets a great seducer as Sherlock falls hard for the charms of dominatrix and ruthless blackmailer Irene Adler (Lara Pulver) in an episode sizzling with unexpected sexual tension. Sherlock scores a victory in their battle of hearts and minds, but only after he mistakenly hands Moriarty one of his greatest coups.</string>
    <string name="s2e2">In this adaptation of the most famous Holmes tale of them all, Sherlock and Watson help a man whose father was supposedly killed by a monstrous hound on Dartmoor, and uncover an MOD conspiracy to develop a hallucinogenic bio-weapon.</string>
    <string name="s2e3">Moriarty uses a powerful new weapon to turn Sherlock’s newfound fame against him. In a memorable rooftop finale, Moriarty convinces Sherlock that only his suicide will save the lives of Watson and Mrs Hudson. And while Moriarty appears to blow his own brains out, Sherlock jumps to certain death… Or does he?</string>
    <string name="s3e1">Two years on from his reported death, Sherlock reappears – to find still grieving pal Watson has moved out and got himself a new friend, Mary Morstan (Amanda Abbington). While John is kidnapped by persons unknown, Sherlock uncovers a terrorist plot to blow up the Houses of Parliament.</string>
    <string name="s3e2">On John and Mary\'s wedding day, awkward best man Sherlock uncovers a plot to murder one of John\'s old Army friends, Major Sholto, at the reception. Sherlock saves the day, and informs the happy couple that they have more good news on the way.</string>
    <string name="s3e3">Sherlock discovers that Mary is a deadly former assassin while trying to retrieve compromising letters from the evil \“Napoleon of blackmail\” Charles Augustus Magnussen. Sherlock\'s efforts to trap Magnussen backfire and he ends up killing him. Banished from Britain by Mycroft, Sherlock is forced to return when his old foe Moriarty appears to return from the grave.</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="cat">CATCH SHERLOCK ON SOCIAL WORLD</string>
    <string name="create"><b>CREATED BY: </b>Steven Moffat , Mark Gatiss</string>
    <string name="based"><b>Based on the works of </b><i>Sherlock Holmes</i> by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle</string>
    <string name="s4e1">As Sherlock waits to see Moriarty\'s next move, he takes on the case of finding someone who is going around and smashing six unique head statues of Margaret Thatcher.</string>
    <string name="s4e2">Sherlock faces one of the most chilling enemies of his long career: the powerful and seemingly unassailable Culverton Smith - a man with a very dark secret indeed.</string>
    <string name="s4e3">Sherlock travels to Europe to escape Moriarty\'s vengeance.</string>
    <string name="duration"><b>Duration : </b>Expected to be 1 hr 28 min</string>
    <string name="ratings"><b>Ratings : </b>N/A</string>
    <string name="reviews">The episode is yet to be aired so no reviews available</string>
    
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
